longwarjournal.org 2013-12-16

# Privacy Policy for the The Long War Journal

| 

The Long War Journal sets the following policies for the use of its sites or services: 

CONSENT TO TERMS 

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this Web site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. The Long War Journal is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The Long War Journal may collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

GATHERING AND USE OF INFORMATION 

The Long War Journal will not collect personally identifiable information from you, other than what you supply to us on a voluntary basis. In order to participate in some activities, you might be asked to provide some personally identifiable information. This could be in connection with the following: 

> • subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as e-mail newsletters)  
>  • requests for membership information  
>  • comments

The Long War Journal will not willfully disclose your personal information to any third party without first receiving your permission. The Long War Journal may use your personally identifiable information for activities explained above, for internal and marketing promotional purposes. 

LOG FILES 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user visits to our site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

LINKS 

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that The Long War Journal is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage readers leaving our site to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. Links to other Web sites are provided as a convenience. By clicking on them, you will be leaving The Long War Journal's Web site. The Long War Journal does not approve or control these sites and does not guarantee the accuracy of their information. 

|   
  
Copyright ©2007 through 2010, Public Multimedia Inc. All Rights Reserved.
